<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Bios on /home/nkallergis/</title>
    <link>https://padavrexi.github.io/bio/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Bios on /home/nkallergis/</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2020 14:23:09 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://padavrexi.github.io/bio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>/home/nkallergis/bio/about</title>
      <link>https://padavrexi.github.io/bio/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2020 14:23:09 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://padavrexi.github.io/bio/about/</guid>
      <description>Unified Skillset primarily focused on networking
Worked as  Network Field Engineer Network Presales Engineer Network Design Engineer Network Automation Engineer  Experienced in  Routing Switching Security Wireless IP Telephony Automation/orchestration Microsoft Azure  Interested in  Automation/Orchestration Network Virtualization NetOps  Tools of choice  VSCode Wireshark Whiteboard Ansible Python Nornir NetBox NAPALM  Contact details LinkedIn * Mail * Phone</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>/home/nkallergis/bio/education</title>
      <link>https://padavrexi.github.io/bio/education/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2020 13:53:54 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://padavrexi.github.io/bio/education/</guid>
      <description> Formal education  Technological Educational Institute of Athens: Dpt of Informatics  Seminars, webinars and courses  &amp;ldquo;Building network automation solutions&amp;rdquo; (ipspace.net)  Certifications  AZ-300 Microsoft Azure Architect Technologies CCSA Check Point Certified Security Administrator CCSE Check Point Certified Security Expert CCNA Cisco Certified Network Associate - Routing and Switching CCIE Cisco Certified Internetwork Expert - R&amp;amp;S (written exam only) CCP-N Citrix Certified Professional - Networking CC-SDWAN Citrix NetScaler SD-WAN Certified  Languages  Greek (native) English (full proficiency) French (limited proficiency) Spanish (limited proficiency)  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>/home/nkallergis/bio/experience</title>
      <link>https://padavrexi.github.io/bio/experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2020 13:53:54 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://padavrexi.github.io/bio/experience/</guid>
      <description>Professional services architect at UniSystems November 2019 - present
As a result of the above and in conjunction with the experience I&amp;rsquo;ve gathered from all my previous positions, my title was changed to &amp;ldquo;Architect&amp;rdquo;. Along with it, my main focus has also shifted mostly towards automation/orchestration and cloud projects for large entities (EU institutions, banks, public sector). In short, I&amp;rsquo;m spending more time in front of VSCode and Azure portal instead of SecureCRT and WireShark.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>/home/nkallergis/bio/projects</title>
      <link>https://padavrexi.github.io/bio/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2020 13:53:54 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://padavrexi.github.io/bio/projects/</guid>
      <description>SYZEFXIS II - ICT October 2020 - present
Technical lead expert for Network &amp;amp; Security Automation Team. Zero-touch provisioning, configuration and change management of WAN, LAN &amp;amp; Security equipment.
Alpha Bank Azure Stack Hub integration project October 2019 - November 2020
Integration of Azure Stack Hub into the bank&amp;rsquo;s traditional data centre. Used Check Point S2S VPN to Cisco ASA. Custom failover/resiliency mechanism using Ansible and Python.
ESMA Migration to Azure October 2018 - May 2020</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>